popmuch.com 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy - PopMuch.com

This Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for PopMuch and applies to the information we collect through www.PopMuch.com (the “Site”). By accessing and/or using the Site, you are consenting to the collection, storage and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy. 

PopMuch reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page so you can readily review the most current version. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how PopMuch is helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of this Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. 

### __   Your IP Address

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When a user requests a page from the Site, our servers will log the user’s current IP address. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site. 

### __   Cookies

This website and PopMuch advertiser products use cookies. A “cookie” is a small text file that contains a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies that may be used: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the “Cookies” folder on your computer and remains in this “Cookies” folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer’s memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site. 

PopMuch uses persistent cookies to serve you personalized advertising. If you would like to opt-out of receiving this personalized advertising, you can click the following link and those ads will no longer be served to you. 

Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site. 

### __   What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site to use our services. 

We will only email you to let you know about important updates and/or changes. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number and other relevant details on your business. 

### __   What do we use your information for? 

Except as provided below under “Disclosures for Legal Reasons”, we will not sell, trade or otherwise provide Personal Information to any third party other than to entities affiliated with PopMuch or vendors we engage to perform functions on our behalf with respect to the Site that are subject to similar restrictions as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will use Personal Information only for the purposes of sending you updates and information regarding the Site and PopMuch products. We may compile and provide aggregate statistics about our Site visitors to third parties, but these statistics will not include any Personal Information. 

### __   How do we protect your information? 

PopMuch is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. You have the right to access and correct the Personal Information you have provided by contacting us at contact@PopMuch.com. 

### __   Protection of Children’s Personal Information

PopMuch is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. 

### __   Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### __   Links

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by PopMuch. Other websites (including those that we may link to) may have their own policies. 

PopMuch has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of any other third party websites. 

### __   Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at contact@PopMuch.com or contact us through our contact form.
